League of Women Voters mss., 1913-2014 LMC 2371
Lilly Library
- Marge and Faber Files
  - Solid Waste (Box 53)
    - Toxic/Hazardous Waste Disposal, 1988-1989 (Box 53)
    - Waste Disposal, 1989 (Box 53)
  - Traffic (Box 53)
    - Bloomington - Master Thoroughfare Plan, 1978 (Box 53)
    - Bloomington - Master Thoroughfare Plan - Map, Undated. (Box 53)
    - Bloomington - Traffic Circulation and Parking Analysis, 1973 (Box 53)
    - Bloomington - Traffic Safety, 2003-2004 (Box 53)
    - Monroe County - Thoroughfare Plan, 1992 (Box 53)
    - "Municipal Strategies to Increase Pedestrian Travel; Final Report" (Washington State Energy Office), 1994 (Box 53)
    - Traffic-Resources, 2001 (Box 53)
  - Utilities (Box 53)
    - Bloomington Utilities Department - In Lieu of Taxes Agreement, 1994 (Box 53)
    - City of Bloomington Utilities (CBU) - Invitation to Present Qualifications for a Wet Weather Management Program for CBU (Sections 1-8), April 1997 (Box 53)
    - City of Bloomington Utilities (CBU) - Invitation to Present Qualifications for a Wet Weather Management Program for CBU (Sections 9-11), April 1997 (Box 53)
    - City of Bloomington Utilities (CBU) - Invitation to Present Qualifications for a Wet Weather Management Program for CBU (Maps), April 1997 (Box 53)
    - City of Bloomington Utilities (CBU) - Rules, Regulations, and Standards of Service (with edits for stormwater), November 1994 (Box 53)
    - City of Bloomington Utilities (CBU) - Rules and Regulations Revision, February 2000 (Box 53)
    - City of Bloomington Utilities (CBU) - Wet Weather Advisory Group, 1997-1999 (Box 53)
    - Utilities Service Board - Background Information, 1974-1984 (Box 53)
  - Wastewater (Box 53)
    - Blucher Poole Wastewater Treatment Plant Improvements - Design Report (Black and Veatch), June 1994 (Box 53)
    - Comprehensive Plan for Water and Sewer Facilities, Monroe County, 1968 (Box 53)
    - Storm Water - Clippings, 1998-1999 (Box 53)
    - Storm Water Management - Resources, 2001-2005 (Box 53)
    - Wastewater - Facilities Plan: Addendum No. 1 to Monroe Regional Waste District (Beam, Longest, and Neff, Inc.), March 1981 (Box 53)
    - Water and Wastewater Planning Priorities, City of Bloomington Utilities, April 1992 (Box 53)
  - Water (Box 53)
    - Data on Indiana Public Water Supplies, 1968 (Box 53)
    - Drinking Water - LWVUS Materials, 1994-1998 (Box 53)
    - Drinking Water - Proposal for Collection and Analysis of Existing Data on Lake Monroe (Daniel Willard and Daniel Levine), 1990 (Box 53)
    - Indiana Conservancy Districts Directory, May 1987 (Box 53)
    - Indiana Statutes Relating to Water Quality, Water Supply and Land Use, 1974 (Box 53)
    - Water Quality Planning - Resources, 1982-1995 (Box 53)
- 2016 Additions
  - Hazardous waste (Box 67)
  - LWV statements regarding Consent Decree, summaries of PCB problem (Box 67)
  - Lake Michigan Inter-League Group (Box 67)
  - Hoosier National Forest [labeled "Solid Waste Slide Show"] (Box 67)
  - Forest Service budget study (Box 67)
  - Water (Box 67)
  - Health care (Box 67)
  - Schools (Box 67)
  - Agriculture (Box 67)
  - LWV-Bloomington board minutes, 1985-1989 (Box 67)
  - LWV-Bloomington board minutes, 1997-1998 (Box 67)
  - Secretary's files (Box 67)
  - Contact info, 1993 (Box 67)
  - Courthouse history (Box 67)
  - "Board meetings, policies, who does what lists, etc." (Box 67)
  - "Media - community reports" (Box 67)
  - Precinct reappropriations (Box 67)
  - "Campaign for a Safer World" (Box 67)
  - Literacy study (Box 67)
  - "Guardian Ad Litum" (Box 67)
  - National Security Units (Box 67)
  - LWVUS national security (Box 67)
  - School finance (Box 67)
  - Literature of LWV Education Fund, (4 folders) (Box 68)
  - Reproductive choice (Box 68)
  - Solid waste management and recycling (Box 68)
  - LWV-Bloomington Member's Handbook (Box 68)
  - "Promoting and Producing Publications" (Box 68)
  - 48th National Convention materials, 2008 (Box 68)
  - The Federalist Papers Reexamined (Box 68)
  - Courthouse information (Box 68)
  - LWV-Bloomington minutes, 1995-1998, (3 folders) (Box 68)
  - City-County Building (Box 68)
  - LWV-IN Council - Richmond, 1990 (Box 68)
  - LWV-IN, "Open the Doors from History to the Future" (Box 68)
  - LWV-IN, "Improving the Quality of Life in Indiana's Hometowns," 1989 (Box 68)
  - LWV-IN, "Building Partnerships" Convention, 1991 (Box 68)
  - "Planning", (2 folders) (Box 68)
  - LWV-Bloomington minutes, 1999-2000 (Box 68)
  - D.C. Amendment - Indiana President (Box 68)
  - LWV-Montgomery County, "Building a Better Community" (Box 68)
    Includes CD-ROM
  - Project LEAP (Box 68)
  - National Convention, "Reaching New Heights," 1988, (2 folders) (Box 69)
  - National Convention, "Making a Difference," 1990, (2 folders) (Box 69)
  - LWV-Bloomington minutes, 2001-2003 (Box 69)
  - State Council, Wabash College, 1998 (Box 69)
  - Madam President 1967 (Box 69)
  - LWV-Bloomington, municipal solid waste update study (Box 69)
  - LWV-IN, various documents and materials, (3 folders) (Box 69)
  - LWV - North Laurence H2O Corp, 1984 (Box 69)
  - Membership Survey - Institute of Social Research Indiana University (Box 69)
  - Health care (Box 69)
  - Lake Monroe, 1985 (Box 69)
  - Engineering Evaluation/Cost Analysis for Winston Thomas Wastewater Treatment Facility, 1997 (Box 69)
  - "Promoting reuse in your community," Monroe County Solid Waste Management, (2 folders) (Box 69)
  - LMV-Bloomington publications, (2 folders) (Box 69)
  - "A Conservationist's Alternative for Hoosier National Forest" (Box 69)
  - PCB (Box 69)
  - LWV-Lexington publication (Box 70)
  - Publications - LMV of US, (2 folders) (Box 70)
  - Indiana State Convention, 1997 (Box 70)
- 2018 Additions
  - Administration
    - Archives - League Records, Lilly Library, 2018 (Box 54)
    - Articles of Incorporation - Ed Fund, 2005-2017 (Box 54)
    - Articles of Incorporation and Merger, 2003-2017 (Box 54)
    - Bylaws, 1989-2002 (Box 54)
    - Bylaws, 2007 (Box 54)
    - Bylaws/Policies - Proposed Changes (Holschuh), 2005 (Box 54)
    - Committees and Positions, 2000-2001 (Box 54)
    - Co-President's Notes, 2010 (Box 54)
    - Copyright Registrations, 1973-2001 (Box 54)
    - Correspondence (Miscellaneous), 1999-2005 (Box 54)
    - Correspondence - LWVUS, 1999-2005 (Box 54)
    - Funding - Ann Diamant Fund, 2007 (Box 54)
    - Funding - Audits, 2012 (Box 54)
    - Funding - Bertina Rudman Gift, 2015 (Box 54)
    - Funding - Finance Drive, 1998-2002 (Box 54)
    - Funding - Finance Drive, 2006 (Box 54)
    - Funding - Finance Drive, 2007 (Box 54)
    - Funding - Finance Drive, 2014 (Box 54)
    - Funding - Finance Drive - Guidelines, undated (Box 54)
    - Funding - Grants - Community Foundation, 2001 (Box 54)
    - Funding - Grants - Computer Award (LWVUS), 2000-2001 (Box 54)
    - History - Clippings and Texts, 1971-2010 (Box 54)
    - IRS - Correspondence, 2005-2010 (Box 54)
    - IRS - Correspondence - Ed Fund, 2005-2011 (Box 54)
    - IRS - Tax-exempt Status, 2012-2017 (Box 54)
    - Liaisons - Bloomington Commission on the Status of Women, 2016 (Box 54)
    - Liaisons - Citizens Advocacy of South Central Indiana, Inc., 2003 (Box 54)
    - Liaisons - Hoosiers for Commonsense Healthcare, 2017 (Box 54)
    - Liaisons - IU Civic Leaders Center (Paul Helmke), 2015-2016 (Box 54)
    - Liaisons - IU Political and Civic Engagement Program (PACE), 2016 (Box 54)
    - Liaisons - Local Council of Women, 1979-2012 (Box 54)
    - Liaisons - Monroe County Youth Services Bureau, 2017 (Box 54)
    - Liaisons - South Central Community Action Program (SCCAP), 1999-2006 (Box 54)
    - Local League Information, 2008 (Box 54)
    - Meeting Record, 2000-2010 (Box 54)
    - Nominating Committee, 2015 (Box 54)
    - Nonpartisanship Policy, 1995 (Box 54)
    - Organization: Information - LWVIN: Tips for Board Members, 1981 (Box 54)
    - Organization: Information - LWVUS: IN League; Guidelines for League Boards, 1980 (Box 54)
    - Organization: Local Board, 1983-1988 (Box 54)
    - Organization: Meetings, 1981 (Box 54)
    - Organization: National Board, 1984 (Box 54)
    - Organization: Newsletter, 1981 (Box 54)
    - Organization: Observers Corps, 1981 (Box 54)
    - Organization: Portfolio - Vice President, 1984 (Box 54)
    - Organization: Responsibilities (Vice President), 1988? (Box 54)
    - Organization: State Board, 1986 (Box 54)
    - Organization: Supplies, 1981 (Box 54)
    - Organization: Units, 1981 (Box 54)
    - Partnerships - Draft Agreement, 2010 (Box 54)
    - Plan Committee - Chairman's Handbook, 1991 (Box 54)
    - Policies and Practices, 1987-2008 (Box 54)
    - Policies and Procedures, 2015 (Box 54)
    - President's File, undated (Box 54)
    - Publicity - Clippings, 1971-1994 (Box 54)
    - Publicity - Clippings and Correspondence, 1991-2000 (Box 54)
    - Publicity - Clippings and Correspondence, 2001-2006 (Box 54)
    - Publicity - Clippings, 2006 (Box 54)
    - Publicity - Clippings, 2007 (Box 54)
    - Publicity - Clippings, 2013-2017 (Box 54)
    - Publicity - LWVBMC Press Coverage, 2015-2016 (Box 54)
    - Statements, Letters to Legislators, etc., 1990-1991 (Box 54)
    - Statements, Letters to Legislators, etc., 1992-1993 (Box 54)
    - Statements, Letters to Legislators, etc., 1994-1996 (Box 54)
    - Statements, Letters to Legislators, etc., 1997-2006 (Box 54)
    - Website, 1997 (Box 54)
    - Website - GoDaddy Contract, 2015 (Box 54)
    - Website Change Proposal, 2009 (Box 54)
    - Who Does What, 2003 (Box 54)
  - Annual Meeting
    - Annual Meeting Booklets, 1980-1989 (Box 54)
    - Annual Meeting Booklets, 1990-1999 (Box 54)
    - Annual Meeting Booklets, 2000-2004 (Box 54)
    - Annual Meeting Booklets, 2005-2009 (Box 54)
    - Annual Meeting Booklets, 2010-2013 (Box 54)
    - Annual Meeting, 2014 (Box 54)
    - Annual Meeting, 2015 (Box 54)
    - Annual Meeting, 2016 (Box 55)
    - Annual Meeting - Budget Committee, 2016 (Box 55)
    - Annual Meeting, 2017 (Box 55)
    - Annual Meeting - Display: 2016-2017 Activities (Box 55)
  - Board of Directors
    - Handbook, 2015 (Box 55)
    - Handbook - Master, 2015 (Box 55)
    - Handbook, 2017 (Box 55)
    - Meetings, 1988 (Box 55)
    - Meetings, 1989 (Box 55)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, 1990 (Box 55)
    - Meetings, 1991 (Box 55)
    - Meetings, 1992 (Box 55)
    - Meetings, 1993 (Box 55)
    - Meetings, 2000-2001 (Box 55)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, May 2004-April 2005 (Box 55)
    - Meetings (Pat Harris), December 2005-April 2006 (Box 55)
    - Meetings (Pat Harris), May-December 2006 (Box 55)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 55)
    - Meetings (Pat Harris), January-April 2007 (Box 55)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, 2006-2007 (Box 55)
    - Meetings (Pat Harris), May-December 2007 (Box 55)
    - Meetings (Pat Harris), January-April 2008 (Box 55)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, 2007-2008 (Box 55)
    - Meetings (Pat Harris), May-December 2008 (Box 55)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, May-December 2008 (Box 55)
    - Meetings (Pat Harris), January-April 2009 (Box 55)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, January-April 2009 (Box 55)
    - Meetings (Pat Harris), May-December 2009 (Box 55)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, May-December 2009 (Box 55)
    - Meetings and Notes (Ann Wrenn), May-December 2009 (Box 55)
    - Meetings (Pat Harris), January-April 2010 (Box 55)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, January-April 2010 (Box 55)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, May-December 2010 (Box 55)
    - Meetings and Correspondence (Ann Wrenn), July-December 2010 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence (Ann Wrenn), January-April 2011 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, May-September 2011 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, October-December 2011 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence (Ann Wrenn), January-April 2012 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence (Linda Shanks), January-April 2012 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence (Ann Wrenn), May-December 2012 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence (Linda Shanks), May-December 2012 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, January-April 2013 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, May-September 2013 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, October-December 2013 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, January-February 2014 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, March-April 2014 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, May-September 2014 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, October-December 2014 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, January-April 2015 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, January-May 2015 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, May-September 2015 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, October-December 2015 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, January-February 2016 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, March-April 2016 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, May-October 2016 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, October-December 2016 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, 14 November 2016 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, 7 January 2017 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, 13 February 2017 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, 15 March 2017 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, 10 April 2017 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, 7 May 2017 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, 12 June 2017 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, 10 July 2017 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, 11 September 2017 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, 13 November 2017 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, 11 December 2017 (Box 56)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, 8 January 2018 (Box 57)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, 12 February 2018 (Box 57)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, 12 March 2018 (Box 57)
    - Meetings Minutes, December 2005-April 2007 (Box 57)
    - Meetings Minutes, August 2007-April 2010 (Box 57)
    - Retreat, October 2013 (Box 57)
    - Training, July 2005 (Box 57)
  - Elections
    - Press Coverage, 2001 (Box 57)
    - Press Coverage, 2010 (Box 57)
    - Press Coverage, 2014 (Box 57)
    - Primary - Press Coverage, February-May 2014 (Box 57)
    - Election - Press Coverage, August-December 2014 (Box 57)
    - City Issues - Press Coverage, 2015 (Box 57)
    - County Issues - Press Coverage, 2015 (Box 57)
    - Ellettsville Issues - Press Coverage, 2015 (Box 57)
    - MCCSC Referendum - Press Coverage, 2015 (Box 57)
    - State Issues - Press Coverage, 2015 (Box 57)
    - Primary - Press Coverage, March-May 2015 (Box 57)
    - Election - Press Coverage, September-November 2015 (Box 57)
    - Election - Press Coverage, October 2015-November 2016 (Box 57)
    - Primary, 2016 (Box 57)
    - City Issues - Press Coverage, 2016 (Box 57)
    - County Issues - Press Coverage, 2016 (Box 57)
    - MCCSC Issues - Press Coverage, 2016 (Box 57)
    - State Legislature - Press Coverage, 2016 (Box 57)
    - Results, 2012 (Box 57)
  - Events
    - Anniversary Celebrations (Box 57)
    - One-Hundredth Anniversary, 2014 (Box 57)
    - Civics and Chill, 2017 (Box 57)
    - County Fair, 2017 (Box 57)
    - Crestmont Family Night Out, 2015 (Box 57)
    - Forums, 1991-2008 (Box 57)
    - July 4 Parade, 1985-1988 (Box 57)
    - July 4 Parade (Reverse Citizens United), 2015-2017 (Box 57)
    - Monroe County Fair, 2017 (Box 57)
    - Teatime with the League (IU P.A.C.E. Program), 2016-2017 (Box 57)
    - Women's History Month Lunch, 1991-2007 (Box 57)
    - Women's History Month Lunch - Nominations, 1991-2007 (Box 57)
    - Women's History Month Lunch, 2016 (Box 57)
    - Women's History Month Lunch, 2018 (Box 57)
  - Membership
    - Brochures, undated (Box 57)
    - Member Handbooks, 1994-2008 (Box 57)
    - Member Honors, 1981-2007 (Box 57)
    - Member Honors - Past President Tea (IU PACE Program), August 2016 (Box 57)
    - Member Lists, 1964-2013 (Box 57)
    - Member Lists, 2013-2015 (Box 57)
    - Member Meeting, 29 January 2015 (Box 57)
    - Member Meeting, 18 February 2015 (Box 57)
    - Member Meeting, 18 March 2015 (Box 57)
    - Member Meeting, 15 April 2015 (Box 57)
    - Member Meeting, 20 May 2015 (Box 57)
    - Member Meeting, 17 June 2015 (Box 57)
    - Member Meeting, 15 July 2015 (Box 57)
    - Member Meeting - LWVUS Constitutional Amendment Study, August-September 2015 (Box 57)
    - Member Meeting, 3 February 2016 (Box 57)
    - Member Meeting, 2 March 2016 (Box 57)
    - Member Meeting, 6 April 2016 (Box 57)
    - Member Meeting, 2 November 2016 (Box 57)
    - Member Meeting, 7 December 2016 (Box 57)
    - Member Meeting, 4 January 2017 (Box 57)
    - Member Meeting, 1 February 2017 (Box 57)
    - Member Meeting, 1 March 2017 (Box 57)
    - Member Meeting, 8 April 2017 (Box 57)
    - Member Meeting, 4 June 2017 (Box 58)
    - Member Meeting, 7 July 2017 (Box 58)
    - Member Meeting, 10 September 2017 (Box 58)
    - Member Meeting, November-December 2017 (Box 58)
    - Member Meeting, 7 January 2018 (Box 58)
    - Member Meeting, 11 February 2018 (Box 58)
    - Member Meeting, 11 March 2018 (Box 58)
    - Member Memorials, 1989-2003 (Box 58)
    - Membership Recruitment and Renewal, 1987-2008 (Box 58)
    - Outreach Items, 2016-2017 (Box 58)
    - Renewal Letters, 2009-2012 (Box 58)
  - Newsletters
    - Newsletter, 1974 (Box 58)
    - Newsletter, 1989 (Box 58)
    - Newsletter, January 1989 (Box 58)
    - Newsletter, 1990 (Box 58)
    - Newsletter, 1991 (Box 58)
    - Newsletters, 1992 (Box 58)
    - Newsletters, 1993 (Box 58)
    - Newsletters, 1994 (Box 58)
    - Newsletters, 1995 (Box 58)
    - Newsletters, 1999-2000 (Box 58)
    - Newsletters, 2000-2001 (Box 58)
    - Newsletters, 2001-2002 (Box 58)
    - Newsletters, 2002-2003 (Box 58)
    - Newsletters, 2003-2004 (Box 58)
    - Newsletters, 2004-2005 (Box 58)
    - Newsletters, 2005-2006 (Box 58)
    - Newsletters, 2006-2007 (Box 58)
    - Newsletters, 2007-2008 (Box 58)
    - Newsletters, 2008-2009 (Box 58)
    - Newsletters, 2009-2010 (Box 58)
    - Newsletters, 2010-2011 (Box 58)
    - Newsletters, 2011-2012 (Box 58)
    - Newsletters, 2012-2013 (Box 58)
    - Newsletters, 2013-2014 (Box 58)
    - Newsletters, 2014-May 2015 (Box 58)
    - Newsletters, June-December 2015 (Box 58)
    - Newsletters, January-June 2016 (Box 58)
    - Newsletters, July-December 2016 (Box 58)
    - Newsletters, January-June 2017 (Box 58)
    - Newsletters, July-December 2017 (Box 58)
  - Observers
    - County Commissioners Staff Time, 2016 (Box 58)
    - Emails and Forms, 1992-2003 (Box 58)
    - Observer Corps, 2015-2016 (Box 58)
    - Observer Reports, 2005-2006 (Box 58)
    - Observing Your Government in Action: Protecting Your Right to Know (LWVUS), 2007 (Box 58)
    - Recognitions, 2014 (Box 58)
    - Who Does What, 2005 (Box 58)
  - Programs
    - Chair's Emails, April-July 2015 (Box 58)
    - Civic Education - Center for Civic Education - Evaluation of the James Madison Legacy Project: Cohort I Teachers, November 2016 (Box 58)
    - Civic Education - Committee Meetings, 2017 (Box 58)
    - Civic Education - Constitution 101, 2017 (Box 58)
    - Civic Education - "Guardian of Democracy: The Civic Mission of Schools", 2015 (Box 58)
    - Civic Education - Indiana Standards, 2016 (Box 58)
    - Civic Education - Standards for US History and Government, 2014 (Box 58)
    - Civic Education - Monroe County Youth Council Project, 2017-2018 (Box 58)
    - Civic Education - Project Citizen Materials (Center for Civic Education), 2008 (Box 58)
    - Civic Education - Students Teaching Students, 2016 (Box 58)
    - Civic Education - We the People Impact Reports, 2015 (Box 58)
    - Civic Education - We the People Project - Indiana Participants (Indiana Bar Foundation), 2016 (Box 58)
    - Committee Meetings and Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 58)
    - Committee Meeting, 26 March 2015 (Box 59)
    - Committee Meeting, 7 April 2016 (Box 59)
    - Healthcare Committee, 2012 (Box 59)
    - Local Program, 1986-1987 (Box 59)
    - Money in Politics - Wendell Potter Event, 1 May 2016 (Box 59)
    - Monroe County Public Library Partnership, 2015-2016 (Box 59)
    - Monroe County Public Library Partnership - Planning and Economic Development, 2015 (Box 59)
    - Monroe County Public Library Partnership - School Finance, 2015 (Box 59)
    - Monroe County Public Library Partnership - State Legislature, 2015 (Box 59)
    - Monroe County Public Library Partnership - Website, 2015 (Box 59)
    - Notes on Policies, Bylaws, and Programs, 2014 (Box 59)
    - Positions, 2009 (Box 59)
    - Positions, 2015 (Box 59)
    - Program Chair, 1994-2006 (Box 59)
    - Program Committee, August 2017 (Box 59)
    - Program Committee Meeting, 7 April 2015 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - Bills in Congress, 2013 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - Bloomington City Council Resolution, September 2016 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - Brennan Center for Justice, 2013 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - "A Citizen's Guide to Redistricting" (Brennan Center for Justice), 2010 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - Common Cause Materials, 2016 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - Common Cause - Meetings and Memos, 2016 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - Congressional Research Service Reports, 2003-2013 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - Events, 2013-2018 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - Events - Gerrymander Meander, 2017 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - Gerrymandering Effects - Indiana, 2016 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - Gerrymandering Effects - Monroe County, 2016 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - Indiana Districts - History, 1837-2016 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - Indiana House Bills, 2017 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - Indiana Maps and Statistics, 2016 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - Indiana Senate Bills, 2017 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - Indiana 2011 Law (HEA 1601) (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - Interim Study Commission, 2016 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - LWVIN Concurrence, 2013 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - Model Reform Criteria (Fair Vote), 2013 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - Monroe County Council Resolution, September 2016 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - New York, 2001-2012 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - Presentations, 2017 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - Readings, 2011-2016 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - Redistricting Reform Conference Report (Airlie, VA), 2003 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - Resources, 2017 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - Rhode Island, North Carolina, 2012-2013 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting - Study Group, 2013-2016 (Box 59)
    - Redistricting Committee, 2017-2018 (Box 59)
    - Solid Waste Study Committee, 1987 (Box 59)
    - Sound Planning Committee, 1990-2005 (Box 59)
    - Voter Education - VOTESMART, 2017 (Box 59)
  - Publications
    - Correspondence, 2001-2003 (Box 59)
    - Government Officials Directory Monroe County, 1976 (Box 59)
    - Guide to Bloomington, Monroe County, Indiana, 1973 (Box 59)
    - Guide to Bloomington, Monroe County, Indiana, 1978 (Box 59)
    - Guide to Bloomington, Monroe County, Indiana, 1980 (Box 59)
    - Guide to Bloomington, Monroe County, Indiana, 1986 (Box 59)
    - Guide to Bloomington, Monroe County, Indiana, 1993 (Box 59)
    - Guide to Bloomington, Monroe County, Indiana, 2001 (Box 59)
    - Guide to Government in Monroe County, 1978 (Box 59)
    - Here is Your Local Government, 1962 (Box 59)
    - Here is Your Local Government, 1967 (Box 59)
    - Here is Your Local Government, 1973 (Box 59)
    - Here is Your Local Government, 1986 (Box 59)
    - Monroe County Government Officials Lists, 1989-1992 (Box 59)
    - Monroe County Government Officials Lists, 1993-1998 (Box 59)
    - Monroe County Government Officials Lists, 1999-2002 (Box 59)
    - Monroe County Government Officials Lists, 2003-2006 (Box 59)
    - Monroe County Government Officials Lists, 2007-2010 (Box 59)